# Diego Mitma Ariza

Frontend Developer Jr. | I Industrial Engineer

## **Contact Information**

diego89ma@gmail.com



51 992 998 907



linkedin.com/in/diegomitari/



github.com/DiegoMitari



diegomitari.github.io/Portfolio/

## **Education**

JavaScript Developer

Coderhouse

Sept 2021 - Nov 2021

Industrial Engineering

National University of San Marcos

2008 - 2015

# **Developed Projects**

#### Credit Simulator | Fintech Bank

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap y JQuery

#### FreeCodeCamp Clone

HTML, CSS, JS, React

#### **Landing Page 01**

HTML, CSS, Flexbox

#### **Landing Page 02 | LigthBox**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## **Employment History**

Deister Software Perú

Jr. Developer Analyst

Jun 2022 - Current

Ramagro (Grupo Gloria) Warehouse Assistant

May 2019 - Aug 2022

Cencosud Retail Perú

**Inventory Analyst** 

Molitalia

Stock Analyst

Nov 2016 - Oct 2018 Jun 2015 - Nov 2016

### **Profile**

Frontend Developer Jr. in continuous learning.

After more than 6 years working as an Industrial Engineer I found my true passion in Web

Development.

I consider myself a curious and self-taught person, adaptable to change and focused on building solutions.

#### Courses

CSS (Flexbox, CSS Grid,

**Bootstrap**)

Udemy

React JS

Platzi

**PostgreSQL** 

Netzun

# **Skills**

**HTML** 

**CSS** Node JS

**JavaScript** React JS

Bootstrap **TailwindCSS** 

PotsgreSQL

Figma

## Languages

English B1 Portuguese A1